Paras Joshi

Bachelor's in computer application

Mobile: +91-8160045635

Parasjoshi2324@gmail.com

+91-9925452324

Career Objective

To give my best in my professional pursuit for overall benefit and growth of the company that I serve by facing the challenges. I will show my calibre and gain some experience. I am willing to my work hard great desire to learn at my profession and want best to my company.

Academic Credentials

Qualification	Board	School Name	Year	Percentage
В. С. А	Saurashtra University	H. J. Doshi It Institute Jamnagar	2019	58.00%
12th	Gujrat bord	Shree D S Gojiya vidhyalay Jamnagar	2014	53.00%
10th	Gujarat Board	Shree D S Gojiya vidhyalay Jamnagar	2012	54.38%

Technical Skills

- I JUST COMPLETED MY 3 MONTH COURSE OF ASP.NET.
- Good knowledge of Database, JS, php, server.
- Expert in WordPress, HTML and CSS.
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft Excel
- Microsoft Power point

Areas of Interest

- WordPress
- PHP
- Code igniter
- Web Development
- HTML & CSS
- ASP .Net

Add on Skills

- Good writing skills in English.
- Good writing and speaking skills in Hindi

Experience

1. Company : icici bank

Designation: gold loan counselors

Duration: 1 st November 2020 to till date

Job profile : sells & marketing for gold loan counseling. Documentation for gold loan

2. Company : B.M. canvasingDesignation : Sales executive

Duration: March 2019 to March 2020

Job profile : Conducting market research to identify selling possibilities and customer needs,

actively seeking out new sales opportunities through cold calling, networking

and social media.

3. **Company** : Speedwell fasteners Jamnagar GIDC

Designation: Computer Operator.

Duration: March 2017 to March 2019

Job profile : Create Billing, Feeling form and bills.

Interpersonal Skills

Ability to rapidly build relationship and set up trust

· Confident and Determined

Ability to cope up with different situations

· Ability of Good Management

Personal Dossier

Permanent Address	C/O Bhimjibhai P Joshi
	Matru Aashish society,
	Street no 2
	B/H. T B hospital
	361008
	Jamnagar
Gender	Male
Date of Birth	9 November, 1996
Languages Known	Gujarati, Hindi, English
Marital Status	Married
Nationality/Religion	Indian
Interest & Hobbies	Computer learning, Volleyball